There's a witch with ashen hair
fluttering in the wind
flying in the air on a broom.
Who is this beauty,
as pretty and lovely as a doll,
who makes even the summer sun
want to shine brighter?
That's right, it's me.
These clothes are pretty hot for this season...
"The Ripper"
It's kind of creepy here...
Hm?
I've gathered you here
today to talk about the crimes.
If you know anything, please tell me.
--Oh, my Bebe's shoes look
like they're about to fall off.
--By crime, does she mean that?
--Oh, my Bebe's shoes look
like they're about to fall off.
--The people who live in this
country really love dolls, huh?
--I'm sure that's what she's talking about.
--The people who live in this
country really love dolls, huh?
--It is, huh?
Those of us in the Association
also consider this a serious matter.
--I'd like your help in
restoring order to this town.
--She's from the United Magic Association?
--I'd like your help in
restoring order to this town.
I changed her clothes today. What do you think?
Oh my, how wonderful.
--Did you get that fabric
from that store over there?
--I wonder if anything happened...
--Did you get that fabric
from that store over there?
--I wonder if anything happened...
--I did. It was expensive, but I splurged.
Lucky. I haven't been able to
get her new clothes for a month.
Well, how about it?
Did you see the Ripper, too?
Huh? The Ripper?
I didn't see the Ripper, but I know
the lives of four women were taken.
Another victim appeared this morning.
This time, it was a woman with green hair.
A fifth?
Just this year.
If we include similar incidents
from the past few years,
there have been more than a hundred.
The lives of over a hundred women...
How unsettling.
What about you?
Yes, I saw clearly.
Please, tell me more!
It happened seven years ago,
on the night of a full moon.
A man became a werewolf--
Hey, come on.
No, I heard the culprit was a cat woman.
No, I heard that the culprit was
a mysterious being, neither male nor female,
from my cousin's friend's
boyfriend's girlfriend.
From who?
What are you saying?!
The culprit is a doll!
It moves in the night, attacking women--
Oh, how terrifying!
I'm going to go hide out at my parents' house!
Oh my, it sounds pretty bad.
Hey, you. Do you have a minute?
Yes? What is it?
Are you a citizen of this country?
No, I'm a traveler.
I'm the Night Witch, Sheila.
As you can probably tell, I'm a witch
sent by the United Magic Association.
I'm the Ashen Witch, Elaina.
So, do you know about the crimes
that happened in this country?
About the Ripper?
Yes, I do.
If you're a traveler, then how do you know?
Because you were asking
the townspeople about it earlier.
Unfortunately, I don't
know anything else about it.
That's too bad.
The people in this town don't know anything.
They just keep saying whatever they want.
If you find out anything, let me know.
I'll be at that assembly hall,
so come find me there.
I don't think I'll find out anything, but okay.
Excuse me.
I know dolls are the country's local specialty,
but they really are everywhere, huh?
"Free dolls"?
They're really amazing.
Welcome to my shop.
The doll--
I made all the dolls in this shop myself!
Your mouth is moving.
If there's one you like,
feel free to take it with you.
Are they really free?
Yup!
Why is that? The store is
so rundown--I mean modest.
It's fine!
I don't care about money!
I just want to see everyone's happy faces!
That's why I make lots of dolls and
give them to the townspeople as presents!
Oh? That's noble of you.
If there's one you like,
feel free to take it, Miss Mage!
I'm not a mage--
Don't hold back. Choose one you like.
Look, how about that one?
It's the most popular one recently.
Um...
I don't have space in my luggage,
but I appreciate the offer.
Well then, excuse me.
Too bad...
To say you don't care about money...
I didn't know there were noble people
with a heart of charity like that...
Right, you'll be in room 5 on the third floor.
Thank you.
There's one here, too...
There we go. Now...
This country is just full of dolls.
All the red brick seems like it
might be bad for my eyes, but--
It's hot...
Oh, that feels good...
Huh? When did I open it...?
Oh, well.
Now, after I eat breakfast,
shall I go to the next... town...?
Who is this?
Huh?
Did you see the Ripper, too?
...I know the lives of four women were taken.
Hair is... a woman's... life...
As you guessed, this is
definitely the work of the Ripper.
Well, yeah. That's what I thought.
I can't believe even a witch
would fall victim to the Ripper...
Well, anyway, I'll take
a look at the scene of the crime.
What should I do?
Just stay there, out of the way.
Hmm... There's nothing here...
There isn't anything
suspicious under the bed, either.
I think the most suspicious thing
in this room is you, Sheila.
I'm not suspicious. I'm conducting a search!
All that's left is that place, huh?
The doll's hair...
Doll?
I put the doll by the bedside into the closet.
I thought so.
Thought what?
All the incidents have had this in common:
The victims were all
attacked while asleep in bed,
the doll inside the room disappeared,
and the doll's hair was scattered in the room.
Why?
The victim's hair probably
became the doll's hair.
The doll...?
The culprit probably
controls the dolls with magic.
So, what'll you do?
What'll I do?
Will you go out and investigate in town?
Of course I will.
Let's catch that cowardly culprit,
cut off their head, and send them
to hell to regret what they did!
You're getting too far ahead of yourself.
Is something the matter?
Hm? Um...
I was just thinking that you're pretty thin.
Now, shall we go?
What was your name again?
I told you already.
I'm Elaina. The Ashen Witch.
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Have a nice day!
What's wrong?
Don't you think that doll's hair
has a really nice texture?
Yeah, I guess. It's like human hair--
If you don't want to get hurt,
then tell us where you got this doll.
I knew it.
This is human hair, isn't it?
Come on, spit it out!
Th-The secret auction...!
Secret auction?
Y-Yes...
A special auction where
special dolls like Little A are sold.
Who are you calling "Little A"?
Where is that secret auction held?!
It's just ahead--
the place where the secret auction is held.
If you hide just your eyes, it's obvious
who's behind the mask, isn't it?
It's getting into the spirit
of things that's important here.
When you put on a mask,
don't you feel like you're doing
something you shouldn't be doing?
Well, the fact that it's a secret auction
should make that obvious already.
Don't say that.
It feels like an opera house.
Apparently, it used to be an opera house.
I'm going to make that doll
Masa's girlfriend today!
I'll definitely win, I'll definitely win,
I'll definitely win, I'll definitely win.
I've been saving up money for the sake of today.
I won't leave until I win.
My cutesy-wootsy...
They're all desperate.
I wonder how they can get
so worked up about some dolls.
I don't really get it, but isn't it the desire
to have unorthodox products
that aren't sold in broad daylight?
It's the moment you've all been waiting for!
We've got tons of wonderful
products for you today, too!
If you've got money, you can buy anything!
Everyone, do you want one?
Yeah!
Without further ado, let's get started!
The first product is this!
So that's what the "unorthodox products" are...
I see!
Fifty!
A hundred!
One hundred! Anyone else?
One-fifty!
Three hundred!
Three hundred! Sold!
All right!
--I wonder if they're all
going to be dolls like that.
--Let's move on. The next one is a gem, too!
--I wonder if they're all
going to be dolls like that.
--Let's move on. The next one is a gem, too!
--No, I don't think so.
Here's the next product!
It is the same.
The third product is this!
Wanna go back?
Now, everyone, thank you for waiting.
The showcase for today's auction is this!
Oh, is it coming?
That doll with the ash-colored hair--
It looks like the one in
the room I was staying in!
Actually, it is the doll that was in my room.
And that's my hair.
Take a look! To make the hair
on these dolls look more real,
they have real human hair!
So it's all hair from the victims.
Calm down, calm down.
They're underestimating me.
They definitely need to die now.
Calm down now. The bidders don't
know how the hair was obtained.
They haven't done anything wrong.
On top of that, these are from the Ripper,
the one everyone's been
talking about on the streets!
How about it? Aren't they amazing?!
Damn it, they're making it hard to help them.
Now, the auction starts!
Wh-What is it?
Her hair's the same color as the doll's.
Could it be...?
You all are enemies of women.
For that crime, you must die.
Ripper, you're here, aren't you?
Please, come out.
You won't come out? I see.
And...
Please, stop!
I can't watch!
That's enough.
Will you stop being mean to my doll, please?
So it was you.
Yup, it was me.
When you visited my shop,
I thought, "That hair is lovely!"
Ha, you don't care about money?
In the end,
you were planning to make all your money
here at the secret auction, weren't you?
No, I really don't care about money.
I always donate the profits
from the secret auction to the poor.
Then, why are you doing this?
Cutting a woman's hair and making her sad,
even though you said you wanted
to see people's happy faces.
That's because...
Because?
It's true that I want to see happy faces!
My special dolls make the bidders here happy,
and when I donate the money from
the auction, it also makes people happy!
Those faces are the best, aren't they?!
But just as amazing are the
faces of people when they're sad,
or mad, or laughing--all their different faces!
Expressions of human emotion
are really wonderful, aren't they?
Oh, I can't contain it any longer!
That angry face of yours is good, too...
Uh, right, that's enough. Now, hang on.
Oh? Miss Mage, I'm actually a witch.
I'm not someone you can win against.
Oh, I'm a witch, too.
Huh?
Unfortunately, this is the end for you.
Hey. Thanks for your help, Elaina.
You're welcome.
Huh? What will you do? What are you doing?
Aren't you mad? Get more mad!
And then show me your face!
No, show me your face!
And so, the case was closed.
The culprit was taken
by the Night Witch, Sheila,
to a branch of the United Magic Association.
She should've gotten the death penalty.
Now, I'll deliver you and get the reward.
Are you happy to get the reward? Are you?
Show me your happy face more--
Is that you, Teach?
What, you were here?
I just got here.
I needed some money,
so I thought I'd find some work.
What did this person do?
She's looking at me with strangely bright eyes.
Oh, so cute!
I'm sure your mad face is even cuter!
Her? Well...
Actually, she's the Ripper,
who went around cutting women's hair.
She's so evil, she even cut
the hair of a traveling witch.
Oh? The hair of a traveling witch?
She had the same pointy hat and necklace as you,
and she had pretty, ashen hair.
Ashen hair. Traveling witch.
I don't know who you are,
but I can tell that you're mad.
Will you tell me more?
Oh, that angry face is so good!
It's the best!